

HAFIDH SYAHPUTRA

Quality Assurance

+62 89 667 887 044

hafidhsyahputra99@gmail.com

Yogyakarta





PROFILE

I am a quality assurance person highly experienced in software testing. I have managed to get the software to pass due diligence using various methods so that no bugs are detected in production. Accustomed to generating Test Case scenarios and locating faults in the website and API.

WORK EXPERIENCES

PLN Icon Plus | September 2023 - December 2023

Quality Assurance Engineer - Internship

I interned as a quality assurance engineer, Creating various automated system tests using tools such as Cypress. What I do:

- 1. Familiar with Agile frameworks scrum
- 2.Create testing documentation

PT. Qatros Teknologi Nusantara | February 2023 - June 2023

Quality Assurance Engineer - MSIB Kampus Merdeka Batch 4 - Internship

I interned as a quality assurance engineer, Creating various automated system tests using tools such as Selenium, and Katalon. What I do:

- 1.Create automated testing scenarios
- 2.Create a testing report
- 3. Create testing documentation

PT. Cerdas Digital Nusantara (CAKAP) | August 2020 - December 2022

Quality Assurance

Cakap is a technology education application development startup from Indonesia that focuses on bold, two-way education. What I do:

- 1. Manual testing of the functionality and usability of mobile apps and web apps in staging and beta phases
- 2. Create a bug discovery report and use Jira
- 3. Familiar with Agile frameworks scrum
- 4. Understand the testing stages in SDLC

EDUCATION

2020 - February 2024
Technical Information

Universitas Teknologi Digital Indonesia I studied at the Indonesian Digital Technology University (previous STMIK AKAKOM) and take Technical. Information Major.

PUBLIC PROJECTS

- https://dafbinikiki.netlify.app Business Intelligence
- https://admin.cakap.com/ Admin Platform
- https://agent.cakap.com/ Commission Platform
- https://corporate.cakap.com/ Corporate Platform

SKILLS

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Strategic
- Thinking
- Analytical Creative Thinking

Technical Skills

- Language :
 - Java, Ruby, Javascript
- · Tools:
 - Selenium, Katalon, Cypress, K6
- · Database:
 - MySQL

ORGANISATIONAL EXPERIENCE

August 2023 - Until Now

Padukuhan Salakan Youth

Publication/Decoration/Documentation

August 2021 - August 2023

Informatics and Computers UKM

Education Division Coordinator

• April 2019 - June 2022

Salakan Organization

Leader